Every time I close my eyes, I see the same scene play out.
Jeez, would you quit walking so fast?
Wait up! I'm family! Don't abandon me, you!
I don't have a family. Leave me alone!
Sorry, no can do.
The director said everyone from the Hakuya Orphanage is family, so shut up and deal with it!
Get off of me!
We are a family, aren't we?
Duh! Of course we are, silly!
One big happy family. Isn't that right, you?
Honestly, you guys are a pain in the butt.
I see the smiling faces of my dearest friends, my family, and then...
I see their bloody, lifeless bodies lying in front of me.
Let you leave us. Get out of here.
Forget about us. Just go.
Hurry.
It never fails. Even after four years, I'm still haunted by my painful memories of that night.
It's the four horsemen of John!
What the hell are you doing here?
Get out of the combat zone, Private Hyakuya!
That's an order!
Who, me? Run away?
Don't count on it.
The only reason I'm here is to get revenge on those blood-sucking freaks.
I can't handle a small fire like this one...
Then I don't have to start to take another breath!
Private, stop!
Initiality
Pực
...
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you, I'm always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame, we're always wet
I'll wait on, take all of the blame, we always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No sun, no light, such a mess, I'm over
Don't kill your wounds, you make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, the change is somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my top, the shadows of the earth
Illusions apart
The golden end is still wrong, but I know it is a pain
I've made a stupid man after
We're all torn to save you for the good show
About your precious work
This is hard to respond to your call
This is a load of crap
I kill a monster and get slapped with a suspension?
They should be promoting me
Not making me rot in this civilian dump
I'm a soldier, dammit
Hey, what are you mumbling about over there?
Do you have something you'd like to add?
If so, then let's hear it
You better shape up, Yakuya
Don't give me any more trouble
I'll have you suspended
What? You'd really kick me out of here?
Awesome!
Well then, I humbly request suspension
How dare you!
Enough!
I won't have you mocking me in front of the class
Sit down and pay attention
What? You got something to say?
Huh?
If you continue to behave uncooperatively
I will have no choice but to report you to the army
And extend your suspension
What?
You've got to be kidding me!
That's it!
One more outburst and I'm sending you straight to them
This sucks! Let me finish!
Start cooperating
Now, where were we?
Ah, yes
I should also point out that your suspension will remain in effect
Until you successfully make a friend
You heard right
So play nice and be a good student
But how can you be a human?
Everyone on the surface died!
That what the vamps told you?
I guess I would have done the same in their shoes
Well, it's true that the virus reduced the world's population by about 90%
And thanks to the trumpets of the apocalypse
An army of bizarre-looking monsters are now roaming the earth
But it will take more than that to wipe out mankind
Our resurrection is underway
Resurrection?
Yep, and that's not all
We have plans to make sure our organization ends up on top
We're going to take back the earth and gather humanity's remnants under one banner
No way
So who are you guys?
Lieutenant Colonel Ichinose
Call me Gurren
I'm with the Imperial Demon Army
Kid, how would you like to come with us and get back at those bloodsuckers?
Put this on him
Tell me
Do you want to get back at the vampires?
I do
If you want your revenge, take my hand
I'll give you all the power you need
More like take my hand and I'll ignore you
You promised me power, Gurren, not a four-year waste of my time
I'm skipping practice
Okay, let's get ice cream on the way home
Wait up, mind if I come along?
I could really go for a cone right now
You just missed a golden opportunity to make some new friends
Are you trying to boss me around?
It's not a good idea
There's that famous attitude I've heard about
According to Lieutenant Colonel Gurren
You avoid social interaction because you lost your family
You're too afraid to engage other people
You fear making connections
Or letting anyone get close to you
Because you're afraid you may lose them
It sounds lonely
Don't you want a girlfriend or maybe a boy?
Look, I'm not afraid of anything
So quit running your mouth and get off my back
I guess you can engage
If you won't shut up, then use your trap for something useful
Like telling Gurren to put me in the vampire extermination unit
I'm ready
Give me the chance to make the fangs bleed for a change
Here, he thought you might say that
So the Lieutenant Colonel told me to give this to you
Now that's what I'm talking about
I knew he hadn't forgotten me
Cherry boys that can't make a friend or a girlfriend
Don't belong in our army
Go out, make one, then introduce them to me
Of course, I'm not gonna hold my breath
Who's he think he is?
You can both go to hell
What are you doing?
Haven't you annoyed me enough?
Stop following me around
Sorry, no can do
I am your army surveillance officer after all
Any violation of army guidelines will be reported
Would you please stop?
Stop what?
I'm just asking you to be a pal
And lend me some money for a snack
Got a problem, Wythe?
Sucks to be him
Whatever, I'm out of here
I'm disappointed in you, Private
You won't make any friends
If you keep turning your back on people in need
What's the hold up?
You want to be friends with us, don't you?
Come on, hand it over
Or I'll stick the vampires on you
What?
You want me to kick your ass?
Hey, give it a rest, you punks
Why?
Who in the hell are you?
What's this?
Showing compassion?
You might just prove your file wrong
Punks, huh?
We got a tough guy
You want to play the hero, is that it?
All right, then
After we beat your face in, you can be our new errand boy
Awesome
See, this is why I love bullies
They're simple and stupid
Okay, want to fight?
Let's go
What?
Oh, I should have mentioned this before
Fighting civilians is prohibited and will extend your suspension
Running errands for those jerks
Why me, man?
Um, I'm sorry
This is all my fault
You've got hands
Help us carry stuff
I'm only here to observe
Sorry
Figures
Please, forgive me
Quit apologizing every two seconds
It's really annoying
What's your problem, anyway?
Why do you let those jerkwads bully you like that?
I'm not being bullied
Oh, right
So he just happened to use your face as a stepping stool
No, it's true
They really aren't bullying me
What?
Yeah
You see, I have a favor I need to ask of Yamanaka
And, well, getting on his good side isn't exactly easy
Which one was Yamanaka?
Seriously?
Are you really that dense?
Yamanaka's the guy who sucker punched you in the face
Oh, him
So, what?
You his fanboy?
No, not exactly
I failed the Imperial Demon Army's entrance exam
I've always wanted to join them
But Yamanaka, he passed with flying colors
He's even being considered for the Moon Demon Company
No freaking way
That guy?
Who wouldn't even let me in?
Corinne, you jerk
You'll pay for this?
So, I was hoping he'd have some connections
If he knows the right people
Maybe I could get another shot at the entrance exam
I know I'm not much of a soldier
And there's no place for weaklings in the army
But
What?
If I join
I can get revenge for my sister
Revenge?
My sister was killed by a vampire
She was trying to protect me
I froze
I wanted to save her, but I couldn't
And so
Moron
If you had helped her, you'd be dead too
Then she would have died for nothing
But
No buts
Let me give you some advice
Don't join the army
Remember
Your sister doesn't want revenge
She's gone
Besides
A wimpy kid like you would only get in the way
We need to kill the fangs, not feed them
Emergency alert
All students and faculty members be advised
A vampire has escaped from the nearby bio-research facility
Why would a vampire want to come here?
If it's in the school, we're as good as dead
You two be quiet
Vampires regain their strength by drinking blood
Both of you, get out of here quickly
I'll call the Moon Demon company and take care of them
Screw them
I'll kill the sucker with my own two hands
What?
You'll have to let me join
I'm gonna make Goron eat his words
Hey, wait a minute
That's suicide
You idiot
Continue the evacuation in an orderly fashion
I repeat
Emergency responders are on report
Whatever
You're a whole idiot
Continue the evacuation in an orderly fashion
The demon army said the city was totally safe
Hey, shut up the wall
Let me get through
Help
To come
It's you.
It's been a while since I've seen a vamp.
I'm going to kill you.
For my family!
Human trash.
Help.
Jamonica! Take this girl and get out of here!
Hurry!
You're a soldier candidate, right?
Hop to it, man!
But I was lying!
What?
I thought if I told everyone that, then they would fear me.
Pesky brat.
Know your place, live stock.
If you're intent on interfering,
then I won't waste time playing with my food!
OK.
What?
I don't know.
creatures that arejolly!
Custom activities,
this is so stupid.
Everybody keeps hitting something.
Listen.
Don't know what.
You're tricking experience.
Unless they're into音.
Go on, ne.
It's good.
The best.
Were you?
I've got some druid in the gear.
And now you can always move the floor this big point.
Yeah.
You just continue to take this off,
so they would have to hit the ceiling.
It's be so done.
Oh dear.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
I can't do it wish.
You might think you're tough, but there's no way you'll ever defeat me.
I'm going to be unstoppable once I've healed myself by drinking her blood.
No!
Are you okay?
Yoichi.
You little...
Good job. That was impressive.
Wow, thank you. But that's what friends are for, right?
I've had enough of you, human!
Yakuya!
Nice try. Did you really think this would kill me? Give me a break. I'm stronger than that.
I think I've earned a little snack for the road.
I'm sorry. You were saying?
How? How do you have a cursed weapon?
All the mighty have fallen. You're pathetic.
And speaking of pathetic, what were you thinking? How'd you plan to kill it with a normal blade and no enchantment? Or were you hoping I'd come to save your sorry ass?
Whatever. I had it. I was about to make my move.
Right.
It's true.
Uh-huh.
Then again, I have to admit you did pretty well for a kid. Thanks to you, the overall damage was minimal.
On top of that, you saved all your friends at school.
Holy crap. That's the Moon Demon Company.
Yeah, yeah. I'm not interested in making friends.
Hey! Now you've seen what I can do. I can kill vampires with the best of them. So make me a part of the company already!
Sorry, but I make it a strict policy not to work with lone wolves.
That's pretty funny coming from the biggest lone wolf in the demon army.
Huh? Did you say something?
No, sir.
Anyway, the rules Shinoa gave you remain the same. If you can't make a friend of this school, then I won't have you join in...
What is it with you trying to force me to make friends? It's not like it's gonna help you kill more vampires.
Oh, thank goodness!
Huh?
Hyakuya! You're alive! I thought you died!
Who's that?
His friend, apparently. Or lover.
Hyakuya? What's wrong? Somebody call an ambulance!
Now that he's met your requirements, you have to keep up your end of the bargain, Lieutenant Colonel.
Huh? What? Are you kidding me?
Every time I close my eyes, I see the same scene play out.
I see the smiling faces of my dearest friends.
My family.
And then...
Ooh, you had us worried there, you.
But I'm glad you made a new friend.
But how are you guys still?
Now we can stop worrying about you.
Don't you get it? We don't want you to live for revenge.
You're way too nice to go through that.
Listen, you need to take good care of your new friend, okay?
Well, we've got to get going.
Hey, what do you mean you're going?
Mika, please don't leave me!
Wait, come back!
Mika!
Yakuya, thank goodness!
Look, Shinoa, he finally managed to wake up!
It's about time.
I have good news.
As of today, you're officially assigned to the Vampire Extermination Unit.
Huh?
Congrats, you! That's awesome!
I almost forgot.
Your enlistment was also accepted.
Welcome to the army, Yoichi.
The two of you made quite an impression on your comrades.
You put your lives on the line and fought bravely.
For people you don't even know.
Gentlemen, welcome to Moon Demon Company.
From now on, you're one of us.
Come on, bring it in, buddy!
This is so stupid.
I'm fine.
Happy?
作詞・作曲・編曲 初音ミク
初音ミク